<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pixliapp</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1792768987646661</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="terms">By signing up, I agree to Pixli\'s terms and conditons, privacy policies and community guidelines.</string>
    <string name="album_heading">Choose a country</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1792768987646661</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Hi bro</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Bye bro</string>
    <string-array name="album_type">
        <item>Wedding</item>
        <item>Travel</item>
        <item>Party</item>
        <item>Other</item>

    </string-array>



    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="terms_title">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="general_info">Pixli Technologies Private Limited, a company incorporated under the Indian Companies Act, 2016 (“Pixli” or the “Company”) has a strong commitment to all of its Users of www.Pixli.in (“Website”), the mobile application ‘Pixli’ as modified from time to time (“App”) and telecommunication media like SMS, email, phone calls etc. (together the “Platform”), including respecting and ensuring that your privacy is protected. In this Privacy Policy, the use of words like “we” or “us” or “our” shall mean an appropriate reference to the Company.\n\n Thank you for taking the time out to read our Privacy Policy. We deeply care about protecting your personal information; hence we take privacy as a serious concern, and are committed in making Pixli a product that people/users love and trust. There are many different ways you can use the services provided by the Platform (“Services”) including but not limited to uploading photos, uploading videos, creating clubs, reacting to photos and connecting with friends. We have prepared this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to inform you of the privacy principles that govern this Platform. Our Privacy Policy outlines the types of information we gather about you, how we use it, how we gather your information and how it is shared, based on your privacy settings. We also let you know the means by which we keep your information secure and the choices you have about the information you choose to share with us. Please read the following to learn more about your privacy policy, we are engaged in giving you transparency of our privacy practices and control over your data.\n\n By accepting this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions, you expressly consent that all your personal information collected by us through the Platform may be used and disclosed as set out in this Privacy Policy and subject to the applicable law and are eligible, as per our Terms and Conditions, to use the Platform, as applicable. If you do not agree please do not use or access the Platform. By accessing the Services you agree to the collection and use of your data by the Company in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. As the Services, we may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your usage of the Platform shall be deemed to be your consent to the Terms and Conditions and the Policies of the Company including this Privacy Policy along with any amendments made thereto by the Company. If you have questions about our privacy practices, please send us an e-mail at legal@pixli.in\n This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms and Conditions. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning as assigned thereto in the Terms and Conditions.\n\n The Privacy Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by the Company or to the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by the Company. For clarity, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by any of the present or future shareholders of the Company.</string>
    <string name="_1_the_information_we_collect">1.The information we collect</string>
    <string name="account_information">Account Information:</string>
    <string name="account_1">When you sign up for Pixli you provide us with your name and email. You will also be able to add a picture of yourself. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you.</string>
    <string name="user_content">User Content:</string>
    <string name="user_1">One of the primary reasons people use Pixli is to share media with others. Examples include when you upload or take a photo, upload or record a video, share your media, create an event, and/or make a comment.</string>
    <string name="transactional_information">Transactional Information:</string>
    <string name="transactional_1">We may retain the details of transactions or payments you make on Pixli. If you do not want us to store your payment source account number, you can remove it using your payments page.</string>
    <string name="contact_information">Contact Information:</string>
    <string name="contact_1">We may offer contact importer tools to help you upload your contacts’ addresses so that you can find your contacts on Pixli, and invite your contacts who do not have Pixli accounts to join. If you do not want us to store this information, please email us at legal@pixli.in with the email address that is associated to your Pixli account. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts information.</string>
    <string name="site_activity_information">Site activity information:</string>
    <string name="site_1">We keep track of some of the actions you take on Pixli, such as adding contacts, uploading media, and indicating you “heart” a piece of media. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us.</string>
    <string name="access_device_and_browser_information">Access Device and Browser Information:</string>
    <string name="access_1">When you access Pixli from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit.</string>
    <string name="cookie_information">Cookie Information:</string>
    <string name="cookies_1">We use “cookies” (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make Pixli easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and Pixli. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to Pixli. We also use them to confirm that you are logged into Pixli, and to know when you are interacting with Pixli applications and websites, our widgets and share buttons, and our advertisements. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use Pixli.</string>
    <string name="_2_how_we_use_the_information_we_collect">2. How we use the information we collect</string>
    <string name="how_1">We use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience. Here are some of the details on how we do that:</string>
    <string name="to_manage_the_service">To manage the service:</string>
    <string name="manage_2">We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. We also use a variety of technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.</string>
    <string name="to_contact_you">To contact you:</string>
    <string name="contact_3">We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. You may opt out of all communications except essential updates on your account settings page. We may include content you see on Pixli in the emails we send to you.</string>
    <string name="email_communications">Email Communications:</string>
    <string name="email_1">If you do not want to receive commercial email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference during the registration process or by making a modification on your account settings page. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as notices regarding this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of Pixli, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from Pixli if your computer supports this type of program.</string>
    <string name="to_make_suggestions">To make suggestions:</string>
    <string name="make_3">We may also suggest that you visit certain spaces and events based on your posts and preferences.</string>
    <string name="when_you_invite_a_contact_to_join">When you invite a contact to join:</string>
    <string name="when_2">When you ask us to invite a contact to join Pixli, we will send your contact a message on your behalf using your name. We may also send up to two reminders to them in your name. You can see who has accepted your invitations, send reminders, and delete your contacts’ email addresses on your invite history page.</string>
    <string name="to_advertise_our_services">To advertise our services:</string>
    <string name="advertise_1">We may ask advertisers outside of Pixli to display ads promoting our services. We may ask them to deliver those ads based on the presence of a cookie, but in doing so will not share any other information with the advertiser.</string>
    <string name="to_offer_joint_services">To offer joint services:</string>
    <string name="offer_1">We may provide services jointly with other companies. If you use these services, we may share your information to facilitate that service. However, we will identify the partner and present the joint service provider’s privacy policy to you before you use that service.</string>
    <string name="_3_how_the_information_we_collect_may_be_shared">3. How the information we collect may be shared</string>
    <string name="information_2">Pixli does not share personally identifiable information with any non- affiliated third parties. Pixli is designed to make it easy for you to find and connect with others. For this reason, your name and profile picture do not have privacy settings. If you are uncomfortable with sharing your profile picture, you should delete it (or not add one).\n\n However we cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community from bad actors. Therefore, we shall disclose your personally identifiable information in the circumstances described below:\n i. We may disclose personal information to appropriate authorities including without limitation the Cybercrime Department or other teams of the relevant State police if the User/s has violated the provisions of the Information Technology Act, 2000 or any other law for the time being in force in India.\n ii. We may also disclose personal information to the concerned authorities under the Information Technology Act, 2000 or any other act for the time being in force in India, if we believe that the User/s is committing any fraud or is doing any illegal activity or is encouraging cyber terrorism or doing any other act which will hamper the national security and integrity of India or of any other country to which the User belongs and/or have accessed to Pixli or violating any law for the time being in force.\n iii. We may disclose personal information in response to a witness summons warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.\n iv. We may disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you).\n v. We may share aggregated statistical data with others for public relations, marketing or other purposes. Such data will not, however, be tied to personally identifiable information.</string>
    <string name="_4_changing_or_deleting_your_information">4. Changing or Deleting Your Information</string>
    <string name="changing_1">Pixli gives you an option to review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided by you at the time of registering with us by changing your “profile settings.” In some cases we may retain your earlier personal information if required by law.</string>
    <string name="_5_user_input">5. User Input</string>
    <string name="user_2">We welcome any User suggestions to assist us in providing new information and services to our users. While we will endeavour to review your suggestions, we may not be able to adequately respond to messages suggesting new ideas. You hereby agree that any idea that you may convey to us shall become our sole and exclusive property and that we will have no liability or responsibility for providing any credit, compensation or other consideration for any idea that you may send to us or for keeping such idea confidential. Such submissions may not be acknowledged and will not be returned.</string>
    <string name="_6_pixli_content">6. Pixli Content</string>
    <string name="pixli_1">The Website may contain text, images, audio-visual productions, opinions, statements, facts, articles, or other information created by us or by third parties (\"Content\"). Such Content is for your reference only and should not be relied upon by you for any purpose. The Content may not be copied, duplicated, distributed, downloaded, sold or otherwise exploited by you in any way, except as agreed to in writing by us. We are not responsible for the Content\'s accuracy and/or reliability.</string>
    <string name="_7_deactivating_and_deleting_your_account">7. Deactivating and Deleting Your Account</string>
    <string name="deactivate_2">i. When you deactivate your account, your account is put on hold. Other users cannot see your profile, but we do not delete any of your information. As you may want to reactivate your account at some point in the future, we do not delete any information from your account. To deactivate your account you can log into your account and in account settings select “deactivate my account”. If you do not re-activate your account within 60 (sixty) days, we can delete your account permanently. Our aim is to maintain our services in such a manner that it protects information from unanticipated or malign destruction. Hence, normally after you delete information from our services, we might not instantly delete remaining copies from our active servers and might not remove information from our backup systems.\n ii. Removing your name or any personal identification from the information: For example, if you choose to deactivate or delete your Pixli account, your name and related information will be removed from the information you have shared.</string>
    <string name="_8_data_retention_and_tracking">8. Data Retention and Tracking</string>
    <string name="data_2">We will retain your personal information and any other information posted, uploaded and/or shared by you for as long as your account is active. If you wish to cancel your account you may delete your account. In case you delete your account with us we may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with any outstanding legal obligations related to any disputes you have with us. Save and except the above, we will immediately delete your information upon request of deletion of account. However you agree and accept that in case of any inquiry from any authorities including without limitation the Cyber Crime Department or other teams of the relevant State police regarding your account or regarding the account of any other User who is connected with you, we will retain your personal information and other such information even if you delete your account. You agree and acknowledge that we will not delete from our servers files that you have in common with other users.\n\n We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on the Platform. We use this information to do internal research on our users\' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include (but not limited to) the information about your computer, browser information, connection information, your IP address, the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Platform or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Platform or not), and statistics of the pages viewed by you i.e. the links you click on the Platform, the number of times you access the page, things you view and other websites you open simultaneously while browsing on ours etc. Your Personal Information allows us to inform you about updates or changes to Services and terms and conditions of providing you the Services.\n\n We use your internet protocol (IP) address to administer the Platform, to help identify you, and to gather broad demographic data. Your IP address contains no personal information about you.\n\n We use data collection devices such as \"cookies\" or other similar devices or technologies on certain pages of the Website and the App, as the case may be, to help analyse our web page flow or App usage, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety.\n\n \"Cookies\" are small files placed on your hard drive (after our web server sends them to your web browser or device through the App) that assist us in providing our services by enabling our web server to collect certain information from the browser or device. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a \"cookie\". We also use cookies for a number of purposes, including to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session, to simplify logging process for registered users, to start a session when logging into our Platform, to enable your browser or device to remember your username between sessions, to enable traffic monitoring, to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are \"session cookies,\" meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive or device at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits (or delete them by looking at the help menu of your browser or device), although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website or App and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or device, or information other than the data you choose to share with us.\n\n Additionally, you may encounter \"cookies\" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website or App that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a \"cookie\" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties (or the resulting information that they record).\n\n When you use one of our location-enabled services (for example, when you access Services from a mobile device), we may collect and process information about your mobile device’s GPS location and the time and/or location information is recorded to customize the Services with location-based information and features. Some of these Services require your personal data for the feature to work and we may associate location data with your device ID and other information we hold about you. We keep this data for no longer than is reasonably necessary for providing services to you. If you wish to use the particular feature, you will be asked to consent to your data being used for this purpose. You can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling the GPS or other location tracking functions on your device.\n\n If you’re using our Services on a mobile device, we may use various devices or other identification files to identify you instead of cookies to save and track your preferences and your use of our applications. Unlike cookies, these identification devices or files may or may not be capable of deletion.\n\n If you choose to avail services on the Platform, we collect information about your browsing or usage behaviour. We also allow other users in the respective clubs to comment about matters shared or posted by you.\n\n IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. The IP address is only used by Pixli on \"need to know\" basis to administer the Platform, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, analyse trends, track user’s movement and it is also used for detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes and for systems administration. Our Web servers also automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. We do not use this information for any other reason except for the reason mentioned above. In the event we need to utilise this information other than the purpose mentioned above we shall take your prior written consent. However we do not share this information with the third parties save and except in cases where the Cyber Law Department of India requires information of the IP address/s of any User under the Information Technology Act, 2000 or such other Act for the time being in force in India.</string>
    <string name="_9_copyrights_trademarks_and_service_marks">9. Copyrights, Trademarks and Service marks</string>
    <string name="copyright_1">Our Website and all materials on this Website including, without limitation, software, images, text, graphics, illustrations, logos, patents, trademarks, service marks, copyrights, photographs, audio, videos and music (the \"Intellectual Property\") are or may be protected under India and worldwide copyrights which are owned or licensed, in whole or in part, by us or otherwise used with permission of their respective owners. Intellectual Property or any third party trademarks, service marks, or copyrights may not be manipulated, edited, reproduced, performed, republished, uploaded to or downloaded from, posted, transmitted, sold, transferred or otherwise distributed or exploited in any manner whatsoever from this Website or any other Website owned or operated by us without our prior written consent, which may be withheld in our sole discretion. Any manipulation of the Website or any portion thereof, or use of any of the foregoing for any other purpose constitutes an infringement of our copyrights, trademark rights or property and proprietary rights, or of the respective owners of such Intellectual Property. Any use of any portion of this Website on any other Website or other networked computer environment is prohibited without our prior written consent, which may be withheld in our sole discretion. You represent that you are the sole author and proprietor of any information or ideas that you submit to us, and that no information or ideas submitted by you has been registered for copyright protection in any jurisdiction or has been previously published in any form.\n\n Users or others that believe their copyright or other rights have been infringed by User Content (\"Claimant\") may provide Pixli’s Designated Agent (identified below) written notice including the following information:\n • An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other interest.\n • A description of the copyrighted work or other work that is alleged to have been infringed.\n • A description of where the User Content that is allegedly infringing is located on the Website.\n • The Claimant’s address, telephone number, and email address.\n • A written statement by the Claimant that he/she/it has a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.\n • A statement by the Claimant, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in the Claimant’s notice is accurate and that the Claimant is the copyright owner or is authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.\n\n Pixli’s Designated Agent for notice of claims of copyright or other forms of proprietary rights infringement can be reached as follows:</string>
    <string name="copyright_2">Pixli, Inc.\n Email: legal@pixli.in</string>
    <string name="copyright_3">If the disputed User Content was posted by a third-party identifiable through reasonable efforts, we will provide reasonable notice to the third-party of the charge. If the third-party responds with a valid counter-notification, we will provide the Claimant with a copy so that the Claimant may take any other steps he/she/it may consider appropriate.</string>
    <string name="_10_security">10. Security</string>
    <string name="security_2">i. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.\n ii. Pixli uses industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored in our servers and/or within our database. We limit the access to this information to those employees who on \"need to know\" basis need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel.</string>
    <string name="_11_our_policy_towards_children">11. Our policy towards Children</string>
    <string name="our_1">Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from persons under 13. Pixli shall not be held responsible and/or liable if you falsely represent and warrant yourself to be of 13 years of age or older. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.</string>
    <string name="_12_other_web_sites_and_services">12. Other Web Sites and Services</string>
    <string name="web_2">We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party\'s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and do not have control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow them to access your content you do so at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="_13_return_policy">13. Return Policy</string>
    <string name="return_2">Pixli will review any/all cases in which user(s) are unhappy with the services, however, we do not issue refunds based on lack of internet/network coverage and/or lack of content posted to an album. Pixli provides you with the tools (mobile application and website) for you and your guests to utilize the album post-event. Furthermore, Pixli provides you with a Dashboard to help you share and promote the use of the application at your event with your guests. If you wish to have your case reviewed, contact support@pixli.in.</string>
    <string name="_14_internal_service_providers">14. Internal Service Providers</string>
    <string name="internal_3">We may use third parties that we refer to as Internal Service Providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on the Platform, including without limitation all kinds of back-end operations, search technology, discussion boards, maintenance services, database management etc. (\"Internal Service Providers\") and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these Internal Service Providers. We expect that these Internal Service Providers would endeavour to use the information we provide them only to facilitate the specific outsourced Platform related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission directly to them for additional uses. In some instances, the Internal Service Provider may collect information directly from You (such as for Platform surveys etc.). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the Internal Service Provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an Internal Service Provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="_15_contacting_us">15. Contacting Us</string>
    <string name="contact_4">If you have any grievances about the quality of service provided by Pixli and/or any other grievance and/ or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact at legal@pixli.in or at 23, IInd Floor, North West Avenue, Club road, West Punjabi Bagh, New Delhi-110026</string>
    <string name="_16_changes_to_our_privacy_policy">16. Changes to our Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="changes_5">Pixli reserves the right to change, update or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws. Pixli has right to amend, modify, add or change the privacy policy from time to time and you shall keep updating yourself with the modified privacy policy. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="community_guidelines">Community Guidelines</string>
    <string name="general_2">We want Pixli to continue to be an authentic and safe place for inspiration and expression. Post only your own photos and videos and always follow the applicable law. Our guidelines play a crucial role and thus we request you to kindly obey these guidelines to keep Pixli running without any difficulty to our other Users. You agree to obey these guidelines when using our products and services (\"Services\"). All capitalised terms used but not defined herein shall have the same meaning as assigned thereto in (i) our Terms and Conditions; or (ii) Privacy Policy, in that order.\n\n We’re committed to these Community Guidelines and we hope you are too. Overstepping these boundaries may result in deleted content, disabled accounts, or other restrictions on the User in accessing the Services. We may investigate and take necessary action from time to time, including deleting User Content or restricting or ceasing a User’s permission to use our Services.\n\n We may alter these guidelines as and when required. So kindly refer to these Community Guidelines regularly.\n</string>
    <string name="unacceptable_use">Unacceptable Use</string>
    <string name="_1_do_not_indulge_in_felonious_activities">1. Do not indulge in Felonious Activities!</string>
    <string name="do_5">Do not use the Site to participate in felonious activities including but not limited to account hijacking, scams, gambling or encourage menacing and/or acts which will harm any person/s and/or any illegal or unlawful acts.</string>
    <string name="_2_do_not_use_malign_products">2. Do not use Malign Products</string>
    <string name="not_5">Do not disseminate viruses, malware, or any other malign or ruinous code that will harm the functionality of the Site.</string>
    <string name="_3_do_not_hijack_other_accounts">3. Do not hijack other accounts</string>
    <string name="hijack_5">Do not access another user’s account without the users’ prior consent. Do not use our products for phishing scams.</string>
    <string name="_4_do_not_circulate_other_s_personal_information">4. Do not circulate other’s Personal Information</string>
    <string name="circulate_5">Do not circulate other people’s confidential details, including but not limited to age, sexual orientation, address, telephone and/or mobile numbers, credit card numbers, personal national ID numbers, or account passwords, without their prior written consent. Information that is already available elsewhere on the Internet or in public records is not considered to be private or confidential under our policies.</string>
    <string name="_5_never_impersonate_or_indulge_in_any_kind_of_fraudulent_behaviour">5. Never Impersonate or Indulge in any kind of Fraudulent Behaviour</string>
    <string name="impersonate_5">The word \'phishing\' is commonly used to describe the offence of electronically impersonating someone else for financial gain. This is frequently done either by using someone else’s login credentials to gain access to protected systems. Do not use our Site to impersonate. You will create an account only for yourself giving truthful information only and not on behalf of another individual. You will not impersonate yourself to be someone else.</string>
    <string name="_6_do_not_use_loathe_speech">6. Do not use Loathe Speech</string>
    <string name="loath_5">Do not upload, post or circulate content that encourages cruelty, insensitivity, dislike or brutality towards groups of people based on their race or ancestral origin, creed, incapacity, gender, age, veteran status, or sexual orientation/ gender identity.</string>
    <string name="_7_do_not_spam">7. Do not Spam</string>
    <string name="spam_5">Do not send spam, including sending undesirable publicizing or commercial data, or undesirable mass solicitation. You shall not create serial accounts for disruptive or abusive purposes, or with overlapping use cases.\n Mass account creation may result in suspension of all related accounts. You may not publish or any third party link which links to malicious content intended to damage or disrupt another User’s browser or computer or to compromise a User’s privacy.</string>
    <string name="_8_never_manipulate_content">8. Never Manipulate Content</string>
    <string name="manipulate_5">Do not manipulate ranking or relevance using strategy like repetitive or deceptive keywords or metadata, offering incentives to review your product or service, or posting fake reviews.\n Do not post or encourage others to post comments which are for any reason whatsoever defamatory, libellous or the like or do not slander, persecute, stalk, intimidate, or which is likely to hurt the religious sentiments of others, or will cause annoyance, inconvenience, danger, obstruction, insult, injury, criminal intimidation, enmity, hatred or ill will or otherwise infringe the legal rights or privacy of others or is in violation of any applicable law for the time being in force.</string>
    <string name="_9_child_protection">9. Child Protection</string>
    <string name="child_5">Do not circulate content that ill-treats children, such as child pornography (including but not limited to cartoon child pornography, child abuse, targets or perpetrators of cyber bullying) or data that represents children in any sexual manner.</string>
    <string name="_10_do_not_post_overly_sexual_uncensored_material">10. Do not post Overly-Sexual Uncensored Material</string>
    <string name="post_5">Do not circulate data that encompasses nudity, graphic sex acts, or sexually uncensored material that are indicated to degrade the allure of human body.\n Do not operate traffic to handle commercial pornography sites. Your profile shall not include adult or derogatory data inappropriate for minors. For example, do not use pictures that exhibit a person’s sexual organs.</string>
    <string name="_11_do_not_resort_to_aggressive_or_bullying_behaviour">11. Do not resort to Aggressive or Bullying Behaviour</string>
    <string name="resort_5">Do not circulate portrayal of unjustified violence.\n Do not menace or bully other users. Online harassment is also an offence and can have serious implications.</string>
    <string name="_12_never_gamble">12. Never Gamble</string>
    <string name="gamble_5">Gambling in India is not permitted. The Information Technology Act, 2000 regulates cyber activities in India and prohibits publication or transmission of information that can corrupt people or illegal or unlawful otherwise.\n Do not give in details that enable online gambling, including sports wager, raffles, or online casinos.</string>
    <string name="_13_legal_rights">13. Legal Rights</string>
    <string name="legal_5">Kindly do not slander, persecute, stalk, intimidate, or otherwise infringe the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others.</string>
    <string name="these_guidelines_are_applicable_to_the_content_you_post_on_our_site">These guidelines are applicable to the content you post on our Site.</string>
    <string name="_14_how_can_you_help_us">14. How can you help us?</string>
    <string name="help_5">i. Each of us is an important part of the Pixli community. If you see something that you think may violate our Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines or other applicable policies, please help us by using our reporting option appearing in your account. Our team reviews these reports and works as quickly as possible to remove content that doesn’t meet any of the Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines or other applicable policies. We may remove content that violates the Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines or other applicable policies or even suspend or terminate the account that has violated the Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines or other applicable policies, depending on the gravity of the violation.\n ii. While addressing your concern or taking any action that you are entitled to, kindly be respectful to others and ensure compliance the Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines or other applicable policies.</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for_using_pixli">Thank You for using Pixli!</string>
    <string name="general_6">This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.\n\n This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and terms and conditions or user agreement for access or usage of www.pixli.in website. This document shall also govern the access and use of the mobile application ‘Pixli’ run by Pixli Private Limited (\'Pixli\'), a company incorporated under the laws of India.\n\n These Terms (\"Terms\") contains rules and regulations, policies and terms and conditions and agreement applicable to any Person who may access or use www.pixli.in, including any sub domains, web pages or extension of www.pixli.in and telecommunication media like SMS, email, phone calls, Mobile App etc. (together the \"Platform\") and you hereby agree and acknowledge to be bound by these Terms.\n\n Pixli’s products and services are provided by Pixli, located at 23, IInd Floor, North West Avenue, Club road, West Punjabi Bagh, New Delhi-110026.By accessing or using the Pixli website, the Pixli Service or any applications (including mobile applications) made available by Pixli, however accessed, you agree to be bound by these Terms. These Terms govern your access to and use of the Platform for services like photo sharing, video sharing, including creation of groups and clubs and that of any products and services offered by Pixli (“Services”). Please read these Terms carefully, and by accessing or using our Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms, by our Privacy Policy and our Community Guidelines. Kindly note that you may access and/ or use Pixli and/or its offered products and/ or services only if you hereby accept to our Terms, Privacy Policy and our Community Guidelines if any stipulated herein.</string>
    <string name="_1_who_can_use_pixli">1. Who Can Use Pixli</string>
    <string name="who_6">It is agreed that currently, you can only use Pixli as an individual for personal use. You cannot create an account on behalf of your business, company, organization or any other entity. Pixli does not allow you to use your account for any commercial activity/s including, but not limited to promotion of any goods and/or services, posting advertisements and/or posting content with a motive of earning profit and/or doing any sort of business of any nature on Pixli. Some of our Products may be in form of software that is downloaded to your computer and you agree that we may automatically upgrade those Services from time to time, and these Terms, Privacy Policy, our Community Guidelines (Pixli\'s User Conduct Policy) with certain modifications will apply to such upgrades.</string>
    <string name="_2_your_pixli_account">2. Your Pixli Account</string>
    <string name="pixli_6">By signing up for a Pixli account, you hereby acknowledge and agree that:\n i. You should be at least 13 years of age while opening an account with Pixli shall not be liable in case of false information being given about the age by the User and the User and/or his natural or appointed guardian alone shall be liable for the consequences as per the law of the country to which the user belongs and as per applicable Indian law. If you are less than 18 years, you hereby acknowledge and agree that your natural or appointed guardian has permitted you to sign up and use the Services.\n ii. You will create an account only for yourself and not on behalf of another individual.\n iii. You will not create more than one personal account.\n iv. You will not impersonate yourself to be someone else. Pixli disclaims all liability arising out of such impersonation.\n v. You will not create another account while your account has been suspended by us or if we have terminated your account.\n vi. You must not create accounts with the Service through unauthorized means, including but not limited to, by using an automated device, script, bot, spider, crawler or scraper.\n vii. You will provide us with accurate, current and complete information about yourself and will keep this information up-to- date at all times. If Pixli has a reason to believe that your Account information is untrue, inaccurate, out-of-date or incomplete, Pixli reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to suspend or to terminate your Account.\n viii. You will not create an account if you are a convicted sex offender.\n ix. You further agree and acknowledge that you are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and/or your account and for restricting access to your account by setting privacy settings so that save and except those users /s whom you allow to view your account no other User/s can view the same. You will neither allow anyone else to use your account nor allow anything that might jeopardize the security of your account. For further information, kindly refer to our Privacy Policy.\n x. You will not post violent, nude, partially nude, discriminatory, unlawful, infringing, hateful, threatening, pornographic or sexually suggestive photos or other content which may incite violence or disturb the peace and integrity of any country including India via the Service.\n xi. You will not defame, stalk, bully, abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate people or entities and you must not post private or confidential information via the Service, including, without limitation, your or any other person\'s financial information or identification numbers or copies that would lead to infringement or violation of other people’s rights or privacy or anything in violation of law.\n xii. You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, files, information, usernames, images, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, sounds, musical works, other works, applications, links and other content or materials (collectively, \"Content\") that you submit, post or display on or via the Service.\n xiii. You will not use the Platform or the Services to do anything unlawful, illegal, malicious or misleading.\n xiv. You will not encourage or cause any other user to violate the Terms, Community Guidelines, Privacy Policy and Fair User Policy and other agreement or terms incorporated herein.\n xv. It is agreed by you that if in the event your password is hacked and/or leaked and/or if your password is disclosed to anyone else Pixli shall not be liable in that case. For the safety of your account information Pixli advises you to change your password frequently. In case you access Pixli through a cyber café or a public computer, Pixli advises you to always sign out and change your password immediately as the same may get hacked or leaked out.\n xvi. Pixli reserves right to terminate your account and deny access of Pixli to any person who violates these Terms and/or Privacy Policy and/or Community Guidelines\n xvii. In the event you refuse to accept these Terms and/ or Privacy Policy and/ or Community Guidelines you shall stop using Pixli immediately.</string>
    <string name="_3_advice">3. Advice</string>
    <string name="advice_6">It is agreed by you that no oral or written information or advice provided by Pixli, its officers, employees, or agents will (i) constitute legal or financial advice or (ii) create a warranty of any kind with respect to the Platform or the services found at the Platform, and users should not rely on any such information or advice for making any decision or abstaining from making any decision.</string>
    <string name="_4_licence">4. Licence</string>
    <string name="licence_6">Pixli gives you a personal, worldwide, limited, royalty-free, non-assignable, non-transferable, non-exclusive and revocable license to use the software provided to you by Pixli as part of the Services. This license is only for the purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the Services provided by us, in the manner permitted by these terms. Upon termination of your account, all licenses and other rights granted to you in these Terms will immediately cease.</string>
    <string name="_5_your_content_in_our_services">5. Your Content in Our Services</string>
    <string name="content_6">i. Pixli Service allows you to post and share content, including photos, videos, text and links (\"User Content\"). You retain all rights in, and are solely responsible for, the content you post on Pixli.\n ii. You grant Pixli and its users a non-exclusive, royalty-free, transferable, sub-licensable, worldwide, perpetual license to use, host, store, display, reproduce, repost, communicate, publish, modify, create derivative works, perform, and distribute your User Content, when you upload or post User Content on Pixli.\n iii. You acknowledge and agree that you give the aforesaid rights to Pixli solely for the purposes of operating, developing, providing, and using the Pixli Services.\n iv. These Terms shall not restrict other legal rights Pixli may have with regard to the posting of User Content. Pixli has right to remove or delete the User Content for any reason whatsoever if Pixli is of the opinion that User Content posted or uploaded on Pixli violates these Terms or our Privacy Policy and other policies. This license continues even if you stop using our Services.</string>
    <string name="_6_monitoring_of_content">6. Monitoring Of Content</string>
    <string name="monitor_6">i. Pixli may monitor any User Content if we have good reason to believe that a person is violating our Terms, Community Guidelines or Privacy Policy.\n ii. If any content posted by you or by any other User on your page on Pixli does not comply with these Terms, Community Guidelines or Privacy Policy and nor does it comply with the Information Technology Act, 2000 any act or any other Law for time being in force in India, then Pixli may remove such content at its sole discretion.\n iii. If Pixli has a reason to believe that the User is a repeat offender, then Pixli may also terminate a User’s access to the Platform. If Pixli terminates your access to the Platform and the Service, Pixli may, in its sole and absolute discretion, remove and destroy any data and files stored by you on its servers and you agree and acknowledge that you shall not hold Pixli responsible and/or liable for removing or deleting such information.</string>
    <string name="_7_mobile_and_other_devices">7. Mobile and other devices</string>
    <string name="mobile_6">i. By using the mobile App of Pixli, you provide consent and all rights necessary to enable you to sync your mobile device or any other device with any information that is visible on Pixli.\n ii. Pixli mobile App is currently free, but you may need to pay the carrier’s regular rates and fees and data charges as applicable.</string>
    <string name="_8_while_using_pixli">8. While Using Pixli</string>
    <string name="while_6">You acknowledge and agree that:\n i. You will comply with the Information Technology Act, 2000 or any other law for the time being in force in India and all other local, state, national and international laws, rules and regulations of the country of which you are a citizen and/or country in which you are accessing Pixli, while uploading any content including but not limited to photos, videos, status’ or comments.\n ii. You must not attempt to restrict another user from using or enjoying the Service and you must also not encourage or facilitate violations of these Terms, Privacy Policy, or the Community Guidelines,\n iii. You agree and acknowledge that you shall not promote, engage or encourage any illegal activity, cyber terrorism, Obscenity, pornography, fraud or misrepresentation arising from such content or shall not post any content contrary to India Law or infringement of copyright of Pixli or any users, invade the privacy of other users, and their publicity rights. In case of breach of any of terms aforementioned Pixli shall not be responsible and/or liable and Pixli shall reserve a right to remove such content/s at its sole discretion.\n iv. You agree that you will not solicit, collect or use the login credentials and/or personal information of other Pixli users.\n v. You agree and acknowledge that you shall not interfere with the operation of Pixli or its services or commit any act which will upload or transmit any virus, worms, bugs, Trojans or any other harmful content which will descript or damage the functionality of Pixli or its software.\n vi. You also agree that you shall not de script or interfere with or harm or violate the security of Pixli or any of its services, system resource, source code, accounts, password ds or networks connected to or accessible through Pixli or any linked sites, if any.\n vii. You must not create or submit unsolicited email, comments, stars or other forms of commercial or harassing communications or spams to any Pixli users.\n viii. You must not change, modify, adapt or alter the Service or change, modify or alter another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with the Service or Pixli.\n ix. You will not use any code language or deceptive language that will lead to suspicion. In case Pixli feels that a language is deceptive or coded, Pixli shall at its sole discretion, intimate to the Cyber Crime Department or other teams of the relevant State police.\n x. You agree to take back-up of all your User Content so that you can access and use it when needed. Pixli does not warrant that it backs-up any Account or User Content, and you agree to accept as a risk the loss of any and all of your User Content.\n xi. You shall not post any objectionable content or comment which is defamatory or any information that is grossly offensive or has menacing character; or any information which you know is false, but for the purpose of causing annoyance, inconvenience, danger, obstruction, insult, injury, criminal intimidation, enmity, hatred or ill-will to other Users, you agree and acknowledge that Pixli shall not be responsible and/ or liable if you do the same.\n xii. You shall not post any comment or link or upload any photo or any other information which threatens or intends to threaten the unity, integrity, security or sovereignty of India or cause injury to the friendly relations with The Foreign States, public order, decency, or morality, or in relation to Contempt of Court, defamation or incitement to an offence. You agree and acknowledge that Pixli shall not be responsible and/ or liable if you do the same.\n xiii. You shall not post any content that discriminates or speaks ill on the grounds of race, religion, national origin, gender, age, marital status, sexual orientation or disability or refers to such matters prohibited by law. You agree and acknowledge that Pixli shall not be responsible and/ or liable for such discrimination.</string>
    <string name="_9_privacy">9. Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_6">At Pixli, we take user privacy extremely seriously. You agree and acknowledge that you have read our Privacy Policy and you are bound by these terms and conditions and also conditions set out in our privacy policy. Employees within the Company may use any information collected from Individual Users for monitoring whether any breach of these Terms and/or Privacy Policy and/or our Community Guidelines is committed by the Users. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our Users. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/ or take civil and/ or criminal proceedings to recover damages against those responsible for breaching the Terms and/or Privacy Policy and/or our Community Guidelines as per Pixli\'s sole discretion and you agree that Pixli may get involved in prosecuting or taking any action in respect of a conflict between the Users for passing any defamatory remarks, libel or slander or uploading any photos or videos. For more information, read our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="_10_copyright">10. Copyright</string>
    <string name="your_copyright_content">Your Copyright Content:</string>
    <string name="copyright_6">i. By uploading any photos and/ or comments and/or videos on Pixli, you represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights of the content that you upload and that it is accurate and that it does not violate these terms or any law for time being in force in India and that it will not cause any inquiry to any person/s or entity. You grant Pixli a royalty – free, perpetual, irrevocable, non – exclusive right and license to use, copy, display, all information you provide to us in any public area of Pixli in any form.\n ii. You agree and acknowledge that Pixli claims no ownership or control over any Content submitted, posted or displayed by you. You represent and warrant that you have all the rights, power and authority necessary to grant the rights granted herein to any content submitted.\n iii. If you believe that somebody is violating your copyright and you want to notify us, you can immediately write to us at legal@pixli.in.\n iv. We may remove any of your content if we believe that it may have been infringed upon someone else’s intellectual property rights, and if you wish to provide any explanation in such a situation you can write to us at legal@pixli.in.\n v. You agree and accept that Pixli shall not be responsible in case of any of infringement of your copyright or trademark or any other intellectual property right.</string>
    <string name="other_s_copyright_content">Other’s Copyright Content:</string>
    <string name="copyright_7">i. You will not use any material or information, including but not limited to photos or videos, which are uploaded on Pixli by the users in any manner that infringes any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, or other proprietary right of any user of Pixli. ii. If you repeatedly infringe other people\'s intellectual property rights, we will disable your account, and when appropriate, delete your account permanently.</string>
    <string name="_11_modification">11. Modification</string>
    <string name="modification_6">i. Pixli shall, at its own discretion have the right to change, modify, add or remove these Terms and/or Privacy Policy and/or our Community Guidelines at any time by giving a 7-day notice and your continued use of the Platform and the Services shall constitute your acceptance of the same. Changes shall be prospective. Pixli shall have the right at any time to change or discontinue or modify any aspect of Pixli\'s website. Such changes and/ or modification and/ or additions and/ or deletion shall be effective immediately upon posting the same on Pixli and any subsequent use of Pixli shall be deemed to have accepted such changes, modification, addition or deletion. You agree that Pixli shall not be liable in respect of any claim/ loss/damage caused to you due to such change, modification, addition, removal, deletion, discontinuance etc. ii. If you choose not to use any of our services, you may do so by unsubscribing such service or by deleting or deactivating your account.\n ii. If you violate these Terms and/or Privacy Policy and/or our Community Guidelines or otherwise create risk of a potential legal proceeding, your account shall be temporarily and / or permanent closed or service/s utilised by you shall be temporary and/or permanently discontinued. We shall notify you by email and shall also give you advance notice of 10 days to access to your data and other information and a chance to retrieve information out of that account and / or Service. Kindly note if the termination of account and / or service shall be owing to your decision simply to delete the account and/or services Pixli shall not give any advance notice to access your data and other information and at once after you terminate your account with us we will delete all your data.</string>
    <string name="_12_transfer_of_data_abroad">12. Transfer of Data Abroad</string>
    <string name="transfer_6">If you are visiting Pixli from a country other than the country in which our server is located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information (including your Account information) across international boundaries. By visiting the Platform and communicating electronically with us and by accepting terms and conditions, you consent to such transfers. By accepting these Terms and/or Privacy Policy, you agree to subject the relationship between Pixli and yourself to applicable Indian law and thereby you agree and acknowledge that none of the laws including in respect of contract between Pixli and you, data privacy etc. of the country where you are based or any other country will apply.</string>
    <string name="_13_disclaimer_of_representations_and_warranties">13. Disclaimer of Representations and Warranties</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_6">You specifically acknowledge and agree that your use of the Platform shall be at your own risk and that the Platform is provided on \"as is\" and \"as available\". Pixli, its officers, directors, employees, contractors and agents disclaim all warranties, statutory, express or implied. Pixli\'s officers, employees, and agents make no representations or warranties about\n (i) the accuracy, completeness, or content of the platform,\n (ii) the accuracy, completeness, or any content of any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the S Platform, and/or (iii) the services found at this Platform or any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the Platform, and Pixli assumes no liability arising out any of the above.\n The foregoing disclaimer of representations and warranties shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by law, and shall survive any termination or expiration of this agreement or your use of the Platform.</string>
    <string name="_14_no_spam">14. No Spam</string>
    <string name="spam_6">It is agreed by you that Pixli has right to immediately terminate any Account which it believes, in its sole and absolute discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any spam or other unsolicited bulk email.</string>
    <string name="_15_limitation_of_liability">15. Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="limitation_6">In no event shall Pixli, its officers, directors, employees, contractors or agents be liable to you or any other person or entity for any direct, indirect, remote, incidental, special, punitive, or consequential damages whatsoever, including any that may result from:\n i. the accuracy, completeness, or content of the S Platform\n ii. the accuracy, completeness, or content of any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the Platform,\n iii. the services found at the Platform or any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the Platform,\n iv. personal injury or property damage of any nature whatsoever,\n v. Third-party conduct of any nature whatsoever\n vi. any unauthorized access to or use of our servers and/or any and all content, personal information, financial information or other information and data stored therein,\n vii. any interruption or cessation of services to or from the Platform or any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the Platform,\n viii. any viruses, worms, bugs, Trojan horses, or the like, which may be transmitted to or from the Platform or any sites linked (through hyperlinks, banner advertising or otherwise) to the Platform,\n ix. any user content or content that is defamatory, harassing, abusive, harmful to minors or any action taken by minors by the use of the Platform or any protected class, pornographic, \"X-rated\", obscene or otherwise objectionable, and/or\n x. Any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of your use of the Platform or the services found at the Platform, whether based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal or equitable theory, and whether or not Pixli is advised of the possibility of such damages.\n xi. The foregoing limitation of liability shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by law, and shall survive any termination or expiration of these Terms or your use of the Platform.</string>
    <string name="_16_confidentiality">16. Confidentiality</string>
    <string name="confidential_6">At Pixli your records, which are not already publicly available or otherwise permitted by you to be disclosed or revealed, are regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, save and except the Cyber Crime Department or other teams of the relevant State police or any other appropriate authority under the Information Technology Act, 2000 (\"the said Act\") and any other applicable law for the time being in force or any directions by such authorities, if required to do so. We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by Pixli will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.</string>
    <string name="changes_to_website_software_and_services">Changes to Website, Software and Services</string>
    <string name="changes_6">Pixli reserves the right to:\n i. change or remove (temporarily or permanently) the Platform or any part of it without notice and you confirm that Pixli shall not be liable to you for any such change or removal.\n ii. change the Terms, Privacy Policy, Community Guidelines, and/or any other Pixli terms or policies at any time by giving a 7-day notice, and your continued use of the Website following any changes shall be deemed to be your acceptance of such change.</string>
    <string name="_17_links_to_third_party_website_s">17. Links to Third Party Website\'s</string>
    <string name="link_6"><![CDATA[Pixli may include links to third party website\'s that are controlled and maintained by others. Any link to other website is not an endorsement of Pixli and you acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the content or availability of any such sites. If you do create a link to a page of this website, you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it. Because Pixli has no control over such Platforms and resources, you acknowledge and agree that the Pixli is not responsible for the availability of such external Platforms or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Platforms or resources. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Platform & to read the terms of use, privacy statements and other policies of these Platform. We advise you to evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to the Platform or accessed through the Platform yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. It is agreed by you that we will not be responsible for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.]]></string>
    <string name="_18_pixli_s_intellectual_property_rights">18. Pixli\'s Intellectual Property Rights</string>
    <string name="intellectual_6">i. You acknowledge that Pixli owns all right, title and interest in and to the Services and the Platform, including all Intellectual Property Rights there in (the \"Pixli Rights\"). Pixli\'s Rights are protected by applicable intellectual property laws. Accordingly, you agree that you will not copy, reproduce, alter, modify, or create derivative works from the Services or the Platform offered by Pixli. You also agree that you will not use any robot, spider, other automated device, or manual process to monitor or copy any content from the Platform. As described below, Pixli\'s Rights do not include third-party content used as part of the Services, including the content of communications appearing on the Services, to which such parties may have rights.\n ii. The Intellectual Property Rights on the Platform and the materials on or accessible via it belong to Pixli or its licensors. The Platform and the materials on or accessible via it and the Intellectual Property Rights therein may not be copied, distributed, published, licensed, used or reproduced in any way (save to the extent strictly necessary for, and for the purposes of, accessing and using the Platform and backing up personal data of the user concerned such as personal photos and videos).\n iii. \'Pixli\' and the Pixli Logo are trademarks, which belong to Pixli and they may not be used, copied or reproduced in any way without written consent from Pixli. For these purposes \"Intellectual Property Rights\" includes the following (wherever and whenever arising and for the full term of each of them, whether registerable or not) any patent, trade mark, trade name, service mark, service name, design, design right, copyright, database right, moral rights, technical knowhow, trade secret and other confidential information, rights in the nature of any of these items in any country, rights in the nature of unfair competition rights and rights to sue for passing off or other similar intellectual or commercial right (in each case whether or not registered) and registrations of and applications to register any of them.</string>
    <string name="_19_indemnity">19. Indemnity</string>
    <string name="indemnity_6">You agree to protect, defend, indemnify and hold harmless Pixli and its officers, directors, shareholders, employees, contractors and agents indemnified, from and against any and all claims, demands, costs, expenses, losses, liabilities and damages of every kind and nature whatsoever imposed upon or incurred by Pixli by whatever name called directly or indirectly arising from:\n i. your use of and access to the Platform;\n ii. your violation of any provision of these Terms, Community Guidelines, Privacy Policy or the policies or agreements which are incorporated herein;\n iii. your violation of any third-party right, including without limitation any intellectual property or other proprietary right and/or\n iv. and for any violation of law of the country you belong to or of the country from where Pixli\'s contents are being accessed or that of any other country where an action may arise in respect of your use of the services and the Platform.\n In case you are younger than 18 years of age, your natural or appointed guardian shall be deemed to have undertaken the aforesaid indemnification obligation in favour of Pixli.\n The indemnification obligations under this para shall survive any termination or expiration of these terms or your use of the Platform or the Services found at the Platform.</string>
    <string name="_20_severability">20. Severability</string>
    <string name="severability_6">In the event that any provision of these Terms is declared by any judicial or other competent authority to be void, voidable, illegal or otherwise unenforceable or indications of the same are received by either you or us from any relevant competent authority, we shall amend that provision in such reasonable manner as achieves the intention of the parties without illegality or, at our discretion, such provision may be severed from these Terms and the remaining provisions of these Terms shall remain in full force and effect.</string>
    <string name="_21_applicable_law_and_dispute">21. Applicable Law and Dispute</string>
    <string name="applicable_6">These Terms, Community Guidelines, Privacy Policy other agreement or terms incorporated herein will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the India, without giving effect to its conflict of law’s provisions or your actual state or country of residence. Any claims, legal proceeding or litigation arising in connection with the Services provided by Pixli will be brought solely in India and Courts in Delhi alone shall have exclusive jurisdiction and you consent to the jurisdiction of such courts.</string>
    <string name="_22_headings">22. Headings</string>
    <string name="heading_6">Headings are included in this Agreement for convenience only and shall not affect the construction or interpretation of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="_23_entire_agreement">23. Entire Agreement</string>
    <string name="entire_6">These Terms, Community Guidelines, Privacy Policy and any other agreement or terms incorporated herein together with any documents expressly referred to in them, contain the entire agreement between us relating to the subject matter covered and supersede any previous agreements, arrangements, undertakings or proposals, written or oral between us in relation to such matters. No oral explanation or oral information given by any party shall alter the interpretation of these Terms, Community Guidelines, Privacy Policy and other agreement or terms incorporated herein. In agreeing to these Terms, you have not relied on any representation other than those expressly stated in these Terms by Pixli and you agree that you shall have no remedy on account of any misrepresentation, which has not been made expressly in these Terms.</string>

    <!-- Terms and policy n guidelines ends here -->
</resources>
